&GT；&GT；史蒂夫：但我首先想到的是这里的小旅馆，对吧。
&gt;&gt; Steve: But the first thing I'm thinking
about, is the lodash over here, right.
即使是gzip它也是23千字节，对吧。
Even gzip it's 23 kilobytes, right.
我碰巧知道写了这个应用程序
I happen to know having written the app,
我正好使用了一种来自洛达什的方法，对吧。
that I am using exactly one
method from lodash, right.
因此，因为我包含了来自洛达什的一种方法，
And so
because I included one method from lodash,
我必须得到所有的小旅馆并支付那笔费用。
I have to get all of lodash and
pay that cost.
那么就有一个关于是否使用lodash的争论了？
So then there's an argument
of do use lodash?
你自己写信吗？
Do you write yourself?
比如，你想在证明洛达什之前在那条路上走多久？
Like, how long do you wanna start walking
on that path before you proven lodash?
缓慢但肯定，如果有更好的方法就好了。
Slowly but surely,
if only there was a better way.
有一些图书馆，
There are some libraries,
这将允许你更具体地说明你需要从他们那里得到什么。
that will allow you to be more specific
about what you need from them.
所以我在这里可以做的是，我可以进入代码，让我们来看看
So what I can do here, is I can go into
the code, and let's take a look for
它在哪里，我相信它在注释视图容器中，不是。
where it is, I believe it's in
the note view container, nope.
&gt；&gt；steve：在那里，把它带进来，来自loadash的下划线，
&gt;&gt; Steve: There it is, bring it in,
the underscore from lodash,
它有洛达什做的所有方法，对吗？
which has got all the methods
that lodash does, right?
就像，我不知道这些天洛瓦什有多少种方法，但是
Like, I don't know how many
methods lodash has these days, but
它足以占据我的可视化工具包中的一大块。
it's enough to take up a large
chunk in my bundle of visualizer.
很酷，所以你可以用loadash做这个很酷的事情，
Cool, so it turns out with lodash
you can do this really cool thing,
我使用的都是Transform方法。
where all I'm using is
the transform method.
因为我有一个带有键和值的对象，我需要一个数组，所以
Cuz I have an object with keys and
values, I need an array, so
我使用的是变换方法，我正在将其转化为这种方法。
I'm using the transform method and
I'm turning it into that.
但我能做的是我可以输入ploash/transform，
But what I can do is I can
type lodash/transform,
现在我们称之为变换。
now we'll just call this transform.
我们会处理掉的。
We'll get rid of that.
首先，这意味着我不需要一直输入那个蹩脚的下划线，
First of all, it means I don't have to
type that lame underscore all the time,
所以这是个胜利。
so that's a win.
让我们继续，重建，看看会发生什么。
Let's go ahead, and
rebuild and see what happens.
&gt；&gt；Steve：建筑很有趣。
&gt;&gt; Steve: Building is fun.
&gt；&gt；steve：我的怀疑是，我会得到一个更小的捆绑。
&gt;&gt; Steve: My suspicion,
is that I'm going to get a smaller bundle.
我们将一起看到这一点。
We will see this together.
&gt；&gt；steve：酷，所以在此之前，这就是我们所拥有的，对吧。
&gt;&gt; Steve: Cool, so before,
this is what we had, right.
现在，代码镜像仍然很大并且负责，但是
Now, code mirror still large and
in charge, but
我们用的是相等的。
lodash we're using lodash that is equal.
Transform不仅仅是Transform，它还使用了一些其他的Loadash方法，所以
Transform is not just transform,
it uses some other lodash methods, so
在这里还没有完全脱离险境。
not totally out of the woods here.
但是，我从500千字节开始，这不是我的300千字节的目标，
But, I went from 500 kilobytes
that's not my 300 kilobyte goal,
想一想这个应用程序有多简单，我已经擦肩而过了
and like think about how simple
this app is I already blew past
300像旁边的酒吧，一个标记下来的笔记和一个编辑器。
300 with like aside bar,
a mark down note and an editor.
这意味着我们现在的500人减少到450人，所以
It means the 500 we're now down to 450, so
通过键入大约10个字符，它将我们捆绑包大小的10%剃掉了。
it's shaved 10% of he size of our
bundle by typing like 10 characters.
我把这叫做胜利，对吧？
I'll call that a win, right?
你可能会说，听着，我用了很多洛瓦什，
And you might be like,
listen I use a lot of lodash,
我不会翻阅文件，然后对每一件事都这样做。
I'm not going through the files and
doing that for every single thing.
幸运的是，你可以作弊，这是一种伟大的，有一个巴别塔
Luckily, you can cheat which is
kind of great, there is a babel
插件，当它编译你的代码时，会自动切换出来。
plugin that when it compiles your
code will automatically switch out.
每次你使用loadash
Every time you use lodash for
要求斜杠什么的，只是为你做所有的事情。
the require lodash slash whatever,
and just do it all for you.
我们可以返回这个代码，&gt；&gt；Steve：原样，
We can turn this code back,
&gt;&gt; Steve: The way it was,
因此，再次招致50千字节税。
so again,
incurring that 50 kilobyte tax again.
我把它放在这个json包里，所以
And I have it in this package json, so
您可以看到它&gt；&gt；steve：babel-plugin-loadash，及其
you can see it
&gt;&gt; Steve: Babel-plugin-lodash, and its
唯一的工作就是做我所做的，在你申请的所有文件中为你做，对吗？
sole job is to do what I did, in all the
files of your application for you, right?
因此，如果你有一个大型应用程序，你会说，我
And so, if you have a large
application and you're like, I
我不想手工做这件事，因为我很擅长这件事，而且外面的感觉很好。
don't want to do this by hand because I'm
to good for that and it's very nice out.
你可以安装这个插件，你可以完成。
You can install this plugin and
you can be done.
所以我们会去babelrc，我们会说插件，
So we'll go to the babelrc,
and we'll say plugins,
我也想使用loadash插件。
I would also like to
use the lodash plugin.
&gt；&gt；Steve：所以请记住我把代码改回原来的样子，
&gt;&gt; Steve: So remember I turned
the code back to the way it was,
我最初是从。
I originally started out with.
所以我希望它基本上会在编译时为我重写代码。
And so my hope is that it will basically
rewriting my code for me at compile time.
我认为一个真正有趣的事情将会发生在网络上
I think one of the really interesting
things that's going to happen to the web
在接下来的几年里，也就是在所有事情发生之前
over the next kinda few years, which
is before everything was happening in
浏览器，比如我们在构建管道中可以做多少事情？
the browser, like how much stuff
can we do in the build pipeline?
我们可以做多少事情，多少优化？
How many things,
how many optimizations can we make?
我们之前看到了优化的JS，现在你可以再次看到它了。
We saw optimized JS earlier,
you can see it again now.
你可以看到这些实际上是无法区分的。
You can see these are effectively
indistinguishable.
代码稍有不同，因为我们重写了它。
The code is slightly different
because like we rewrote it.
但我从原始代码开始，我使用了Babel插件，
But I started with the original code,
I used the babel plugin,
我仍然有我的50千字节的储蓄，对吧，太好了。
I still get to have my 50
kilobyte savings, right great.
好吧，但这里还有其他罪犯，
All right, but
there are some other culprits in here,
就像我们都能看到房间里的大象一样。
like we can all see
the elephant in the room here.
现在是谁的问题？
Who's the problem right now?
Codemirror是问题所在，codemirror正在解决
Codemirror is the problem,
codemirror is accounting for
我的标准尺寸，甚至我的js尺寸，狮子分享。
of my par size, or
even my js size, the lions share.
是162千字节，gzip 53，对。
It's pars 162 kilobytes, gzip 53, right.
这又一次，实际上就像我捆绑的三分之一，对吧。
That is again, effectively like
a third of my bundle, right.
再次，如果他们从来不点击编辑，他们将永远不会使用这个代码。
And again, if they never click on edit
they will never even use this code.
他们会交税来赦免它，他们会支付下载它的税，
They will pay the tax to parson it,
they will pay the tax of downloading it,
他们永远不会真正使用它，而且我的应用程序会快得多，而且
they will never actually use it, and
my app would be a lot snappier and
如果我没有这样做，加载速度会更快。
quicker to load if I just didn't do this.